<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Unchained</string>
    <string name="loading_auth_link">Loading Authentication…</string>
    <string name="please_visit">Please visit\u0020</string>
    <string name="link">Link</string>
    <string name="using_code">using the code</string>
    <string name="copy_code">Copy code</string>
    <string name="code_copied">Code copied to clipboard</string>
    <string name="or_visit">Or directly visit</string>
    <string name="waiting_user_auth">Waiting user authorization</string>
    <string name="obtained_user_auth">Obtained user authorization</string>
    <string name="waiting_secret">Waiting Secret</string>
    <string name="waiting_token">Waiting token confirmation</string>
    <string name="obtained_token">Obtained token</string>
    <string name="waiting_link">Loading authorization link</string>
    <string name="link_loaded">Authorization link loaded</string>
    <string name="premium">Premium</string>
    <string name="not_premium">Not Premium</string>
    <string name="premium_points_format">Premium Points: %1$d/1000</string>
    <string name="premium_days_format">Remaining days: %1$d</string>
    <string name="user">User</string>
    <string name="new_download">New Download</string>
    <string name="remote_traffic">Remote Traffic</string>
    <string name="password_optional">Password [Optional]</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="unrestrict">Unrestrict</string>
    <string name="invalid_url">Invalid URL</string>
    <string name="loading">Loading</string>
    <string name="copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="open_link">Open Link</string>
    <string name="copy_link">Copy Link</string>
    <string name="link_copied">Link Copied</string>
    <string name="streaming">Streaming</string>
    <string name="megabytes_short">MB</string>
    <string name="file_size_format">%1$d MB</string>
    <string name="file_size_format_kb">%1$.2f KB</string>
    <string name="file_size_format_mb">%1$.2f MB</string>
    <string name="file_size_format_gb">%1$.2f GB</string>
    <string name="selected_file_size_format">%1$d MB / %2$d MB selected</string>
    <string name="size_error">Error getting the file size</string>
    <string name="torrent_status_format">Status: %1$s</string>
    <string name="speed_format_b">%1$d b/s</string>
    <string name="speed_format_kb">%1$.1f KB/s</string>
    <string name="speed_format_mb">%1$.1f MB/s</string>
    <string name="speed_error">Error getting the download speed</string>
    <string name="load_streams">Load streams</string>
    <string name="apple" translatable="false">Apple</string>
    <string name="dash" translatable="false">Dash</string>
    <string name="liveMP4" translatable="false">Live MP4</string>
    <string name="h264_webm" translatable="false">H264 WebM</string>
    <string name="quality">Quality</string>
    <string name="links">Links</string>
    <string name="add_private_token_message">You can also use your private API token from https://real-debrid.com/apitoken, which will allow you to utilize every functionality, such as streaming.</string>
    <string name="add_private_token">Add Private Token</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="private_token">Private Token</string>
    <string name="invalid_token">Please check the token value</string>
    <string name="download_details">Download Details</string>
    <string name="authenticate">Authenticate</string>
    <string name="upload_torrent">Upload Torrent</string>
    <string name="error_loading_torrent">No torrent loaded</string>
    <string name="link_or_magnet">Link or Magnet</string>
    <string name="status">Status</string>
    <string name="magnet_error">Magnet Error</string>
    <string name="magnet_conversion">Magnet Conversion</string>
    <string name="waiting_files_selection">Waiting Files Selection</string>
    <string name="queued">Queued</string>
    <string name="downloading">Downloading</string>
    <string name="downloaded">Downloaded</string>
    <string name="error">Error</string>
    <string name="virus">Virus</string>
    <string name="compressing">Compressing</string>
    <string name="uploading">Uploading</string>
    <string name="dead">Dead</string>
    <string name="download">Download</string>
    <string name="lists">Lists</string>
    <string name="torrent">Torrent</string>
    <string name="user_avatar">User Avatar</string>
    <string name="buy_premium">Buy Premium</string>
    <string name="paste">Paste</string>
    <string name="streamable">Streamable</string>
    <string name="open_stream">Open stream</string>
    <string name="upload_torrent_description">Upload a .torrent file from your local memory</string>
    <string name="upload_file_description">Upload a .torrent file or a RSDF, CCF, CCF3, DLC container from your phone</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="file_id_format">ID: %1$s</string>
    <string name="file_type_format">Type: %1$s</string>
    <string name="rd_settings_link_description">Manage your user settings, premium state, and convert points from your account page.</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="content_description_settings">Settings for the application</string>
    <string name="error_unrestricting_download">Error while un-restricting the download</string>
    <string name="internal_error">Internal error</string>
    <string name="bad_parameter_value">Bad parameter value</string>
    <string name="missing_parameter">Missing parameter</string>
    <string name="unknown_method">Unknown method</string>
    <string name="method_not_allowed">Method not allowed</string>
    <string name="slow_down">Slow down</string>
    <string name="resource_unreachable">Resource unreachable</string>
    <string name="resource_not_found">Resource not found</string>
    <string name="bad_token">Bad token</string>
    <string name="permission_denied">Permission denied</string>
    <string name="tfa_needed">Two-Factor authentication needed</string>
    <string name="tfa_pending">Two-Factor authentication pending</string>
    <string name="invalid_login">Invalid login</string>
    <string name="invalid_password">Invalid password</string>
    <string name="account_locked">Account locked</string>
    <string name="account_not_activated">Account not activated</string>
    <string name="unsupported_hoster">Unsupported hoster</string>
    <string name="hoster_in_maintenance">Hoster in maintenance</string>
    <string name="hoster_limit_reached">Hoster limit reached</string>
    <string name="hoster_temporarily_unavailable">Hoster temporarily unavailable</string>
    <string name="hoster_not_available_for_free_users">Hoster not available for free users</string>
    <string name="too_many_active_downloads">Too many active downloads</string>
    <string name="ip_Address_not_allowed">IP Address not allowed</string>
    <string name="traffic_exhausted">Traffic exhausted</string>
    <string name="file_unavailable">File unavailable</string>
    <string name="service_unavailable">Service unavailable</string>
    <string name="upload_too_big">Upload too big</string>
    <string name="upload_error">Upload error</string>
    <string name="file_not_allowed">File not allowed</string>
    <string name="torrent_too_big">Torrent too big</string>
    <string name="torrent_file_invalid">Torrent file invalid</string>
    <string name="action_already_done">Action already done</string>
    <string name="image_resolution_error">Image resolution error</string>
    <string name="torrent_already_active">Torrent already active</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="account_page">Account Page</string>
    <string name="login_type_open">Logged in with the open token. Some features such as transcoding are unavailable.</string>
    <string name="login_type_private">Logged in with private token. All features are available.</string>
    <string name="api_needs_private_token">This function requires a private API token</string>
    <string name="torrents">Torrents</string>
    <string name="downloads">Downloads</string>
    <string name="torrent_not_downloaded">Torrent not ready yet</string>
    <string name="feedback_summary">Report technical issues or suggest new features</string>
    <string name="feedback_title">Send feedback</string>
    <string name="credits_title">Credits</string>
    <string name="license_title">License</string>
    <string name="license_gpl" translatable="false">GPL-3.0</string>
    <string name="terms_title">Terms of use</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="credits_text">
        <![CDATA[
            <body>
                <p>
                    Various projects, resources, and people have helped in the creation of this app. A thank goes to:
                    <br>
                    <ul>
                    <li> Real Debrid people for all their work </li>
                    <li> @oathzed for testing every nooks and cranny of the app</li>
                    <li> rawpixel.com for inspiring the logo and symbols with the <a href="https://www.rawpixel.com/image/843352/minimal-logo-designs-set" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">minimal logo design set</a> </li>
                    </ul>
                </p>
            </body>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="terms_text" translatable="false">
        <![CDATA[
            <body>
                        <p>
                          By downloading or using the app, these terms will
                          automatically apply to you – you should make sure therefore
                          that you read them carefully before using the app. You’re not
                          allowed to copy, or modify the app, any part of the app, or
                          our trademarks in any way. You’re not allowed to attempt to
                          extract the source code of the app, and you also shouldn\'t try
                          to translate the app into other languages, or make derivative
                          versions. The app itself, and all the trade marks, copyright,
                          database rights and other intellectual property rights related
                          to it, still belong to LivingWithHippos.
                        </p> <p>
                          LivingWithHippos is committed to ensuring that the app is
                          as useful and efficient as possible. For that reason, we
                          reserve the right to make changes to the app or to charge for
                          its services, at any time and for any reason. We will never
                          charge you for the app or its services without making it very
                          clear to you exactly what you’re paying for.
                        </p> <p>
                          The Unchained app stores and processes personal data that
                          you have provided to us, in order to provide my
                          Service. It’s your responsibility to keep your phone and
                          access to the app secure. We therefore recommend that you do
                          not jailbreak or root your phone, which is the process of
                          removing software restrictions and limitations imposed by the
                          official operating system of your device. It could make your
                          phone vulnerable to malware/viruses/malicious programs,
                          compromise your phone’s security features and it could mean
                          that the Unchained app won’t work properly or at all.
                        </p> <!----> <p>
                          You should be aware that there are certain things that
                          LivingWithHippos will not take responsibility for. Certain
                          functions of the app will require the app to have an active
                          internet connection. The connection can be Wi-Fi, or provided
                          by your mobile network provider, but LivingWithHippos
                          cannot take responsibility for the app not working at full
                          functionality if you don’t have access to Wi-Fi, and you don’t
                          have any of your data allowance left.
                        </p> <p></p> <p>
                          If you’re using the app outside of an area with Wi-Fi, you
                          should remember that your terms of the agreement with your
                          mobile network provider will still apply. As a result, you may
                          be charged by your mobile provider for the cost of data for
                          the duration of the connection while accessing the app, or
                          other third party charges. In using the app, you’re accepting
                          responsibility for any such charges, including roaming data
                          charges if you use the app outside of your home territory
                          (i.e. region or country) without turning off data roaming. If
                          you are not the bill payer for the device on which you’re
                          using the app, please be aware that we assume that you have
                          received permission from the bill payer for using the app.
                        </p> <p>
                          Along the same lines, LivingWithHippos cannot always take
                          responsibility for the way you use the app i.e. You need to
                          make sure that your device stays charged – if it runs out of
                          battery and you can’t turn it on to avail the Service,
                          LivingWithHippos cannot accept responsibility.
                        </p> <p>
                          With respect to LivingWithHippos’s responsibility for your
                          use of the app, when you’re using the app, it’s important to
                          bear in mind that although we endeavour to ensure that it is
                          updated and correct at all times, we do rely on third parties
                          to provide information to us so that we can make it available
                          to you. LivingWithHippos accepts no liability for any
                          loss, direct or indirect, you experience as a result of
                          relying wholly on this functionality of the app.
                        </p> <p>
                          At some point, we may wish to update the app. The app is
                          currently available on Android – the requirements for
                          system(and for any additional systems we
                          decide to extend the availability of the app to) may change,
                          and you’ll need to download the updates if you want to keep
                          using the app. LivingWithHippos does not promise that it
                          will always update the app so that it is relevant to you
                          and/or works with the Android version that you have
                          installed on your device. However, you promise to always
                          accept updates to the application when offered to you, We may
                          also wish to stop providing the app, and may terminate use of
                          it at any time without giving notice of termination to you.
                          Unless we tell you otherwise, upon any termination, (a) the
                          rights and licenses granted to you in these terms will end;
                          (b) you must stop using the app, and (if needed) delete it
                          from your device.
                        </p> <p><strong>Changes to This Terms and Conditions</strong></p> <p>
                          I may update our Terms and Conditions
                          from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page
                          periodically for any changes. I will
                          notify you of any changes by posting the new Terms and
                          Conditions on this page.
                        </p> <p>
                          These terms and conditions are effective as of 2020-09-23
                        </p> <p><strong>Contact Us</strong></p> <p>
                          If you have any questions or suggestions about my
                          Terms and Conditions, do not hesitate to contact me
                          at livingwithhippos@gmail.com.
                        </p> <p>
                          This Terms and Conditions page was generated by
                          <a href="https://app-privacy-policy-generator.firebaseapp.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">App Privacy Policy Generator</a></p>
            </body>
    ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="privacy_text" translatable="false">
        <![CDATA[
        <body>
    <strong>Privacy Policy</strong> <p>
                  LivingWithHippos built the Unchained app as
                  an Open Source app. This SERVICE is provided by
                  LivingWithHippos at no cost and is intended for use as
                  is.
                </p> <p>
                  This page is used to inform visitors regarding my
                  policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal
                  Information if anyone decided to use my Service.
                </p> <p>
                  If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to
                  the collection and use of information in relation to this
                  policy. The Personal Information that I collect is
                  used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with
                  anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
                </p> <p>
                  The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings
                  as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at
                  Unchained unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.
                </p> <p><strong>Information Collection and Use</strong></p> <p>
                  For a better experience, while using our Service, I
                  may require you to provide us with certain personally
                  identifiable information. The information that
                  I request will be retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.
                </p> <!----> <p><strong>Log Data</strong></p> <p>
                  I want to inform you that whenever you
                  use my Service, in a case of an error in the app
                  no data is collected. It just crashes!
                </p> <p><strong>Cookies</strong></p> <p>
                  Cookies are files with a small amount of data that are
                  commonly used as anonymous unique identifiers. These are sent
                  to your browser from the websites that you visit and are
                  stored on your device\'s internal memory.
                </p> <p>
                  This Service does not use these “cookies” explicitly. However,
                  the app may use third party code and libraries that use
                  “cookies” to collect information and improve their services.
                  You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies
                  and know when a cookie is being sent to your device. If you
                  choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some
                  portions of this Service.
                </p> <p><strong>Service Providers</strong></p> <p>
                  I may employ third-party companies and
                  individuals due to the following reasons:
                </p> <ul><li>To facilitate our Service;</li> <li>To provide the Service on our behalf;</li> <li>To perform Service-related services; or</li> <li>To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.</li></ul> <p>
                  I want to inform users of this Service
                  that these third parties have access to your Personal
                  Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to
                  them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to
                  disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
                </p> <p><strong>Security</strong></p> <p>
                  I value your trust in providing us your
                  Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially
                  acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method
                  of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic
                  storage is 100%% secure and reliable, and I cannot
                  guarantee its absolute security.
                </p> <p><strong>Links to Other Sites</strong></p> <p>
                  This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on
                  a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note
                  that these external sites are not operated by me.
                  Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the
                  Privacy Policy of these websites. I have
                  no control over and assume no responsibility for the content,
                  privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or
                  services.
                </p> <p><strong>Children’s Privacy</strong></p> <p>
                  These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13.
                  I do not knowingly collect personally
                  identifiable information from children under 13. In the case
                  I discover that a child under 13 has provided
                  me with personal information, I immediately
                  delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian
                  and you are aware that your child has provided us with
                  personal information, please contact me so that
                  I will be able to do necessary actions.
                </p> <p><strong>Changes to This Privacy Policy</strong></p> <p>
                  I may update our Privacy Policy from
                  time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page
                  periodically for any changes. I will
                  notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on
                  this page.
                </p> <p>This policy is effective as of 2020-09-23</p> <p><strong>Contact Us</strong></p> <p>
                  If you have any questions or suggestions about my
                  Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact me at livingwithhippos@gmail.com.
                </p> <p>
                  This privacy policy page was created at
                  <a href="https://privacypolicytemplate.net" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">privacypolicytemplate.net</a>
                  and modified/generated by
                  <a href="https://app-privacy-policy-generator.firebaseapp.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">App Privacy Policy Generator</a></p>
    </body>
    ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="premium_needed">A premium subscription is required to do this</string>
    <string name="premium_needed_torrent">A premium subscription is required for magnet and torrents</string>
    <string name="downloading_torrent">Preparing torrent, please wait…</string>
    <string name="please_insert_url">Please insert a magnet or a link</string>
    <string name="please_login">Please log in your account</string>
    <string name="loading_magnet_link">Loading magnet link…</string>
    <string name="loading_torrent_file">Loading torrent file…</string>
    <string name="unchained_torrent_download">Unchained Torrent Download</string>
    <string name="unchained_plugin_download">Unchained Plugin Download</string>
    <string name="temporary_torrent_download">Temporary download of a torrent file</string>
    <string name="temporary_plugin_download">Temporary download of a plugin file</string>
    <string name="error_loading_dialog">Error loading the dialog, please reopen it.</string>
    <string name="title_theme_preference">Theme</string>
    <string name="automatic">Automatic</string>
    <string name="night">Night</string>
    <string name="day">Day</string>
    <string name="title_various">Various</string>
    <string name="original">Original</string>
    <string name="night_theme">Night mode</string>
    <string name="title_aspect">Aspect</string>
    <string name="delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="torrent_removed">Torrent removed</string>
    <string name="open">Open</string>
    <string name="content_description_delete_torrent_item">Remove the torrent item</string>
    <string name="content_description_delete_download_item">Remove the download item</string>
    <string name="torrent_details">Torrent Details</string>
    <string name="download_removed">Download removed</string>
    <string name="press_again_exit">Press back again to exit</string>
    <string name="content_description_share_download">Share download link</string>
    <string name="share">Share</string>
    <string name="share_with">Share download link via:</string>
    <string name="restart_to_apply">Restart to apply</string>
    <string name="remove">Remove</string>
    <string name="confirm_download_removal_description">Are you sure you want to remove the download? This action cannot be undone.</string>
    <string name="yes_remove">Yes, remove it</string>
    <string name="confirm_torrent_removal_description">Are you sure you want to remove the torrent? This action cannot be undone.</string>
    <string name="confirm_item_removal_description">Are you sure you want to remove this item? The action cannot be undone.</string>
    <string name="confirm_removal">Confirm removal</string>
    <string name="multiple_links_warning">This torrent has multiple links. Check the downloads list to find all of them.</string>
    <string name="percent_format" translatable="false">%1$d%%</string>
    <string name="theme_day_support">This theme supports only the day mode</string>
    <string name="app_not_installed">App not installed. Check your settings.</string>
    <string name="limitations">Error: your phone is limiting background activity.</string>
    <string name="open_link_format">Open %1$s link</string>
    <string name="copy_link_format">Copy %1$s link </string>
    <string name="open_with_format">Open %1$s with Kodi</string>
    <string name="yatse" translatable="false">Yatse</string>
    <string name="loading_host_link">Loading host link</string>
    <string name="title_debugging">Debug</string>
    <string name="update_regexps">Update hosts link matcher</string>
    <string name="updating_link_matcher">Updating link matcher…</string>
    <string name="unknown_error">Unknown error</string>
    <string name="network_error">Network error</string>
    <string name="torrent_channel_description">Notification channel for torrents download status</string>
    <string name="torrent_in_progress">Torrent download in progress</string>
    <plurals name="seeders_format">
        <item quantity="one">%d seeder</item>
        <item quantity="other">%d seeders</item>
    </plurals>
    <string name="seeders_string_format">seeder/s: %s</string>
    <string name="torrent_in_progress_format">%1$d%% - %2$.2f MB/s</string>
    <string name="download_complete">Download complete</string>
    <string name="unknown_status">Unknown Status</string>
    <string name="downloading_torrent_format">Downloading %1$d torrents</string>
    <string name="monitor_torrents_download">Monitoring torrents download</string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="enable_torrent_monitoring_title">Enable torrent monitoring</string>
    <string name="alternative_link">Alternative link</string>
    <string name="parsing_error">Error parsing the server response</string>
    <string name="content_description_search">Filter the lists</string>
    <string name="search">Search</string>
    <string name="loading_torrent">Loading torrent</string>
    <string name="referral">Referral</string>
    <string name="referral_summary">Use a referral when clicking on the account page button</string>
    <string name="decline">Decline</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept</string>
    <string name="referral_proposal">You can support this app by navigating to your account page by using a referral link. We\'ll bother you only once; you can change your choice in the settings.</string>
    <string name="to_authenticate">\u0020to get authenticated\u0020</string>
    <string name="this_link">this link</string>
    <string name="login_message_placeholder">Please visit this link to get authenticated</string>
    <string name="host_match_not_found">No matching host found. Refresh hosts from settings if needed.</string>
    <string name="refreshing_token">Refreshing authentication, please retry in a bit</string>
    <string name="black_and_white">Black and white</string>
    <string name="open_browser_stream">Stream in browser</string>
    <string name="folder">Folder</string>
    <string name="files_list">Files List</string>
    <string name="error_loading_folder">Some links couldn\'t be loaded</string>
    <string name="plugin">Plugin</string>
    <string name="search_files">Search Files</string>
    <string name="magnet">Magnet</string>
    <string name="error_loading_file">Error loading file</string>
    <string name="category">Category</string>
    <string name="category_all">All</string>
    <string name="category_anime">Anime</string>
    <string name="category_software">Software</string>
    <string name="category_games">Games</string>
    <string name="category_movies">Movies</string>
    <string name="category_music">Music</string>
    <string name="category_tv">TV shows</string>
    <string name="category_books">Books</string>
    <string name="open_github">Open Github</string>
    <string name="plugin_description_message">"On this screen you'll be able to search for torrent and magnet files. Aside from the basic plugins available, you'll find more on the internet with the extension '.unchained', download and then open them with this app. Try the official GitHub repository for starters."</string>
    <string name="search_plugins">Search Plugins</string>
    <string name="get_search_plugins">Get search plugins</string>
    <string name="delete_plugins">Delete external plugins</string>
    <string name="delete_plugins_summary">Remove all the plugins installed by the user</string>
    <string name="plugin_removed">%1$d plugin/s removed</string>
    <string name="plugin_install_error_newer">The plugin is already installed with a newer version</string>
    <string name="plugin_install_installed">Plugin installed</string>
    <string name="plugin_install_not_installed">Plugin not installed</string>
    <string name="no_links">No links</string>
    <plurals name="magnet_format">
        <item quantity="one">%d magnet</item>
        <item quantity="other">%d magnets</item>
    </plurals>
    <plurals name="torrent_format">
        <item quantity="one">%d torrent</item>
        <item quantity="other">%d torrents</item>
    </plurals>
    <plurals name="links_format">
        <item quantity="zero">No links</item>
        <item quantity="one">1 link</item>
        <item quantity="other">%d links</item>
    </plurals>
    <plurals name="plugins_version_old_format">
        <item quantity="one">1 plugin needs an update. Check for a new version</item>
        <item quantity="other">%d plugins need an update. Check for a new version</item>
    </plurals>
    <string name="seeders_short_format" translatable="false">S: %s</string>
    <string name="leechers_short_format" translatable="false">L: %s</string>
    <string name="size_format">size: %s</string>
    <string name="leechers_string_format">leecher/s: %s</string>
    <string name="delete_all">Delete all</string>
    <string name="delete_all_downloads_message">Are you sure you want to delete all your downloads? This action cannot be undone.</string>
    <string name="delete_all_torrents_message">Are you sure you want to delete all your torrents? This action cannot be undone.</string>
    <string name="torrents_removed">Torrents removed</string>
    <string name="removing_torrents">Removing torrents…</string>
    <string name="downloads_removed">Downloads removed</string>
    <string name="removing_downloads">Removing downloads…</string>
    <string name="version">Version</string>
    <string name="download_started">Download started, check the notification bar</string>
    <string name="download_not_started">Error during download initialization</string>
    <string name="download_not_started_format">Error initializing download of %s</string>
    <string name="needs_download_permission">Unchained needs the storage permission to download files directly</string>
    <string name="kodi" translatable="false">Kodi</string>
    <string name="test_connection">Test the connection</string>
    <string name="kodi_credentials_incomplete">At least IP and port are required for Kodi</string>
    <string name="ip_address">IP address</string>
    <string name="port">Port</string>
    <string name="username">Username</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="kodi_connection_successful">Kodi connection successful</string>
    <string name="kodi_connection_error">Kodi connection error</string>
    <string name="port_range_error">Port must be between 1 and 65535</string>
    <string name="kodi_configure_credentials">Please configure Kodi in the app settings</string>
    <string name="kodi_remote_control">Kodi remote control</string>
    <string name="enable_kodi_control">Read here for instructions on how to set up Kodi for remote control (usually enabled in system->services->control). After that complete the required fields below</string>
    <string name="only_if_auth">Required only if the authentication is enabled in Kodi</string>
    <string name="rd_status">Real Debrid status</string>
    <string name="show_kodi">Show Kodi button</string>
    <string name="only_big_files">Only big files</string>
    <string name="filter_type">Only media files (avi etc.)</string>
    <string name="sort">Sort</string>
    <string name="file_size_filter">Filter for the files size</string>
    <string name="file_size_filter_description">Minimum size in MB for the \"Only big files\" option in the folder screen</string>
    <string name="container">Container</string>
    <string name="error_parsing_container">Error parsing the container</string>
    <string name="loading_container_file">Loading container file…</string>
    <string name="no_network_connection">No network connection</string>
    <string name="download_all">Download All</string>
    <string name="sending_crash_report">Unchained just crashed.\nSending crash report…</string>
    <string name="upload">Upload</string>
    <string name="unsupported_file">File not supported</string>
    <string name="hoster">Hoster</string>
    <string name="retry_login">Retry</string>
    <string name="generic_login_error">An error occurred during login. You can check your connection, try again in a while, or log in from real-debrid.com for more information.</string>
    <string name="retry_later">Retry later</string>
    <string name="overlay_title">Overlay</string>
    <string name="overlay_summary">Let this app overlay over others</string>
    <string name="content_description_plugins_link">Link to plugins page</string>
    <string name="get_plugins">Get more plugins</string>
</resources>